X

Privacy Policy
==============

We do not want your personal informations beside a working email address

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

The customer is solely responsible for any breaches of security affecting servers under customer control. If a customer’s server is involved in an attack on another server or system, it will be shut down and an immediate investigation will be launched to determine the cause/source of the attack. In such event, the customer is responsible for the cost to rectify any damage done to the customer’s server and any other requirement affected by the security breach.

What data do we collect
-----------------------

For users who register on our website, placed an order or used the contact form, we store their email address and the name they gave.  
Submitting your name is completely optional and do not need to be accurate, we will never ask your to verify this information.

Customers who choose to pay with Credit Card expose themselves to share the  identity tied to their Credit Card with Servers.Guru. We encourage crypto-currency payments and especially Monero in order to  minimize the leak of personal informations to Servers.Guru.

All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time. Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

We do not use cookies beside a “remember me” cookie for registered users currently logged in on Servers.Guru

Embedded content from other websites
------------------------------------

Page on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.  

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

The contact form is checked through an external automated privacy respecting spam detection service (Hcaptcha).

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

We do not send or sell your data anywhere or to anyone.  

Copyright © 2021-2024 Moula World LLC  
All Rights Reserved.

Our Services
------------

About Us
--------

Contact Us
----------

#### Tor:

**servers.guru**: [srvguru7bjzzjba7xy2hnx2ju4k77qy4eum2h3tgudwc3j2zof4aggyd.onion](http://srvguru7bjzzjba7xy2hnx2ju4k77qy4eum2h3tgudwc3j2zof4aggyd.onion/)

**my.servers.guru**: [mysguru5rigppyihrnsejsa2wb3vv35wlzvx5u7bahw2uld3rxycphqd.onion](http:// http://mysguru5rigppyihrnsejsa2wb3vv35wlzvx5u7bahw2uld3rxycphqd.onion)

[Telegram](https://t.me/serversguru) [\[email protected\]](https://servers.guru/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[](https://matrix.to/#/@servers.guru:matrix.servers.guru)
